Guide to the Alan Sondheim Papers MSS.267
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IV. Film and Video Recordings, 19 Linear Feet in 17 record cartons, 2 flat boxes, and 4 oversize film cans.; 35 film reels including 20 8mm films, 1 super 8 film, 13 16mm films, and 1 35mm film.; 74 videoreels (1/2 inch); 94 videocassettes (u-matic); 7 videocassettes (betamax); 1 videocasse
  - World War II Canadian Training Film, Undated (Box 79, 16mm film reels 267_022)
  - Wormhole Model, 1971 (Box 19, Half inch video reel 267_474, Box 18, Half inch video reel 267_547)
    Tape 267_474 is labeled as the original recording. Tape 267_547 also includes a recording of "Scan."
  - Wupatki, 1990 (Box 9, Vhs 267_688)
  - You, Undated (Box 8, Vhs 267_721)
  - You Wouldn't Believe, Undated (Box 16, Hi8 267_413, Box 9, Vhs 267_698)
  - Young Deconstructor (Box 15, Hi8 267_444,, Box 16, Hi8 267_410)
    267_444's label says "Master / Color / Bridge (No One Listens)"
  - [Illegible Title], Undated (Box 9, Vhs 267_687)
  - [No Title], undated (Box 21, Vhs 267_659)
- Series V. Exhibitions and Events, 4 Linear Feet in 5 manuscript boxes and 3 flat boxes.; 1 film reels 16mm film; 1 sound tape reels; 8 audiocassettes; 13 videoreels (1/2 inch); 5 videocassettes (u-matic); 19 videocassettes (vhs); 2 videocassettes (minidv); 11 videocassettes (hi8); 46.6 Gigabytes in 55 digital files.
  Series V. Exhibitions and Performances includes ephemera, documentation, photographs, and recordings from exhibitions and performances. Sondheim's multimedia work has been exhibited internationally and digitally, in spaces including Track 16 Gallery in Los Angeles, the Grand Central Art Center, and Second Life Odyssey. He has also collaborated extensively with Swiss choreographer and dancer Foofwa d'Imobilité (Frederic Gafner), as well as many other dancers, often using tools like motion capturing technology to explore themes of embodiment in cyberspace.
  This series is arranged chronologically. Wherever possible, record titles were taken directly from Sondheim's work.
  - Exhibit Photographs, circa 1960-1995 (Box 75, Box 74, Box 76, Box 63, Box 83, Folder 16)
  - "Oratory Called Green", 1967 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - "Wood 1968" Exhibit, Rhode Island School of Design Gallery (Box 84, Folder 20)
  - Exhibits, Screenings, and Events by Various Artists - Ephemera, Flyers, and Exhibition Catalogs, 1968-2006 (Box 71, Folder 1, 2)
  - Symmetry Diagrams for Aborted Gain Ground Gallery Show, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Project for Going [Illegible] Gallery, 1969-1970 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - High Voltage Exhibit - Rhode Island School of Design, 1969-1972 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Perceptual Extention ceNTer, circa 1970 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Franklin Furance - Event Ephemera, circa 1970-1990 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - 4-3-2-0 Spacing at Brown University / Conversation / Space Stream, 1971-1972 (Box 18, Half inch video reel 267_546)
    The tape's label says, "1. 4320 Brown University Meta-4 Computer; Charles Strauss Programmer 1971; Andrea Kovass / Beth Cannon; Conversation - John Woodson / Alan Sondheim; Four Overlays, 1972; Space Stream Marge Anderson, 1971; College Blog R.I.S.D."
  - "Strata," Nova Scotia College of Art and Design, 1972 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - David Humphrey and Diane Brown Exhibition Slides, 1972-1991 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - 4-3-2-0 Spacing: Brown University, 1973; cuid21360 (Box 20, Half inch video reel 267_482)
  - Crystal Pond / Air Gallery - Rosemary, May, 1973; EIAJ standard (Box 17, Half inch video reel 267_528, Box 20, Half inch video reel 267_490)
  - Discussions: Works / Words Exhibition Series, Institute for Art and Urban Resources, 1974 (Box 83, Folder 17)
  - Alan Sondheim Profile by Kil Schwartz [Illegible] NYC, October 8, 1975; cuid34934 (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_324)
    Duration: 54 minutes; Preservation note: Audio has a muted quality.
  - Lives: Artists Who Deal With Peoples' Lives (Including Their Own) As the Subject and/or the Medium of Their Work by Jeffrey Deitch, 1975 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Exhibition Planning - Proposals, Correspondence, Notes, circa 1975-2005 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Far Hills Project, 1975 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - "The New American Filmmakers Series" Calendar, Whitney Museum of American Art, 1976 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - ZBS Residency, 1976 (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Exhibit Photographs, 1976-1987 (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence from Artists with Enclosed Artwork and Exhibition Ephemera, 1976-1995 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Theses After Marx / Red Art Brigade Whitney Show, 1976; cuid21361 (Box 17, Half inch video reel 267_510, 267_522, 267_526, 267_527, Box 19, Half inch video reel 267_475)
  - Blank Tape - Museum of Modern Art Showing, October, 1976 (Box 20, Half inch video reel 267_494)
  - Film Screenings - Flyers, Press Releases, Postcards, 1977-2001 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - "Contradictions and Prerogatives" Exhibit Catalog, Raw Gallery, 1978 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Dance / Visual Arts Program, 1978; Duration: Approx. 24 min (Box 7, U-matic 267_648)
  - VIDEO / TAPE: Tape prepared for talk at Ontario Gallery of Art, February 2, 1978; cuid30330 (Box 20, Half inch video reel 267_518, Box 68, Folder 15)
    Includes original label and playback log in Box 68.
  - "A Space/Harbourfront/222 Warehouse" Installation Poster, July 1980 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Quebec Country Western Reading, July 10, 1980; cuid34894 (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_285)
  - "Video Vis a Tergo" Exhibition Poster, 1980 (Box 84, Folder 15)
  - Atlanta Biennial - Photographs, circa 1980-1990 (Box 73, Folder 13, Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Millennium Film Workshop - Event Ephemera, Written Pieces, Press, circa 1980-1990 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Mike Metz - Visual Art, Exhibit Catalogs, 1980-1992 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Alan Sondheim and Laura Hayes Film Screening Poster, 1980-1995 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, Flyers, Ephemera, 1980-2006 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Exhibition Statements, circa 1980-2006 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Israel Bond Event - Presentation to Evelyn Sondheim by Judge Max Roseun, Response by Evelyn Sondheim, November 22, 1981; cuid34889 (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_279)
  - Sections 1-8 of First Film Series - Supporting Materials for Guggenheim Application, 1981-1982; Duration: Approx. 50 min (Box 1, U-matic 267_568)
    The tape's label says, "Alan Sondheim, sections 1-8 of first film series, 1981-1982, from 16mm optical sound black and white. This series consists of 40+ segments, made at the rate of one reel per week, edited in-camera. They deal with ideology, politicization, the position of the subject, and are made to be shown together."
  - Film Screenings at Art Metropole (Toronto, Canada) - Ephemera, 1981-1983 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Millennium Film Workshop Inc. Personal Cinema Program Calendars, 1983-1993 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Newport Harbor Art Museum Events Calendar, July-August 1983 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - AIR Program (ZBS Studios), 1984 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Cinematheque San Francisco Calendar, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Nexus Contemporary Art Center - Event Posters, 1984-1985 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Nexus Contemporary Art Center - Event Posters, 1984-1987 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Nexus Contemporary Art Center - Event Ephemera, 1984-1987 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Nexus Contemporary Art Gallery - Atlanta Biennale Press Coverage, 1984-1987 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - American Indian Pow-Wow - Grand Prairie, Texas, September 7, 1986; cuid34834 (Box 25, 8mm film reel 267_135)
  - Halwalls - Event Notes, Ephemera, Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Film Forum Calendar, Los Angeles, CA, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - "Louise Shaw Makes a Case for Nexus," Open City, June 1987 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - "Immure" Exhibition at the Atlanta Stockade - Photographs, 1987 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Nexus Contemporary Art Center - Atlanta Biennale Press Coverage, 1987 (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Tre Roberts Exhibition, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Exhibits, Screenings, and Events by Various Artists - Posters, 1987-2010 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Exit Art International Forum of Super 8, 1988 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Western New York Filmmakers Forum - Screening Flyers, 1988 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - "The Figure When It's Speaking" Catalog Essay - World Gallery, 1989 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Tyler Stallings Exhibition Slides, 1989-1995 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Film Screenings at Image Film/Video, Atlanta, GA - Ephemera, 1990 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - "Photophobia" Video Exhibition, 1990 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - "The Red Year" Exhibit, Western Carolina University, 1990 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Nexus Exhibition, Includes Opening - Atlanta, January 11, 1991 (Box 14, Hi8 267_382)
  - Selections: Exhibition Consideration Tape: Desperate Thought Rises to the Surface, 1991; Duration: 1 hour 50 min, From Hi8 PCM Stereo (Box 8, Vhs 267_741)
  - Virtual Arm Project - Stelarc, 1992-1993 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Aplets No Mister by Frederic Gafner, December, 1993; Duration: 26 min (Box 7, Vhs 267_660, Box 9, Vhs 267_685)
  - Nexus, September 11, 1993 (Box 16, Hi8 267_404)
  - Exhibition Master: Rainbow @21, Millenium 1994 (Box 8, Vhs 267_739)
  - One0One by Frederic Gafner, September, 1994 (Box 6, U-matic 267_632, Box 7, U-matic 267_649, Box 9, Vhs 267_690, Box 10, Vhs 267_777)
  - Nihon Coin Over by Frederic Gafner, 1994-1995; Duration: 25 min (Box 8, Vhs 267_705, Box 9, Vhs 267_693)
  - On the Vivid by Foofwa D'Imobilité, 1996; Duration: 29 min (Box 9, Vhs 267_700)
  - Stelarc Photographs and Interview, 1996-2001; cuid39855 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_180)
  - Maximax (Work in Progress) by/with Foofwa d'Imobilité, 1997; Duration: 6 min (Box 9, Vhs 267_701)
  - Carte Blanche by Foofwa d'Imobilité, Loup Geneve, 1998 (Box 8, Vhs 267_707)
  - Improvisation at Hot House P.S. 122 - Alan Sondheim and Foofwa D'imobilite, December 6, 1998 (Box 10, Vhs 267_748)
  - Performance in Paris by Foofwa d'Imobilité, February, 1999 (Box 9, Vhs 267_673)
  - Performance in Hellerau by Foofwa d'Imobilité, June 5, 1999 (Box 9, Vhs 267_684, Box 68, Folder 20)
    Includes event flyer in Box 68.
  - Terpsicorp and Marlabor by Foofwa d'Imobilité, September, 1999; Duration: 32 min; color (Box 8, Vhs 267_726, 267_715, Box 9, Vhs 267_676, 267_689, Box 10, Vhs 267_743)
    267_676 is labeled as the "original three performances." 267_689 is labeled as "quickcam shots." 267_743 is labeled as "rough cuts."
  - Catalog Essays and Exhibit Ephemera, 1999-2009; cuid39849 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_171)
  - Dance Performances and Choreographed Videos, 2000-2009; cuid39851 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_174)
  - Event, Exhibition, and Performance Photos, 2000-2009; cuid39853 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_178)
  - Anya Olenbacher Dance with Rehearsal, 2003 (Box 14, Minidv 267_379)
    This tape is labeled as the master recording.
  - One0One by Frederic Gafner - Edit, 2003 (Box 7, Vhs 267_664)
  - Dance Photographs, 2003-2009; cuid39852 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_175)
  - Nom d'artiste: Foofwa d'Imobilite, 2004 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - "not-doing" Exhibit at the Paul Mesaros Gallery - Photos, 2004; cuid39845 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_167)
  - "2 Fine" Performance, 2005; cuid39856 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_228)
  - "Open Studio" Event Photos, 2005; cuid39846 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_168)
  - Foofwa d'Imobilite - Bio and Performance Ephemera, 2005-2006 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - "Descendance" Dance Series - Artwork, 2006; cuid39841 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_163)
  - "em/bedded" Exhibit at Track 16 Gallery, 2006; cuid39842 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_164)
  - "Flute" Performance - Photos and Audio Recordings, 2006; cuid39844 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_166)
  - Foofwa d'Imobilite - Dance Photos, 2006 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - "Incidences" - Five Dances by Foofwa d'Imobilite, 2006; cuid39861 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_233)
  - "Terpsicorp" Dance Series - Artwork, 2006; cuid39847 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_169)
  - 123 Club Performances - Audio and Video Recordings, 2007-2008; cuid39848 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_170)
  - SecondLife Events - Screenshots and Videos, 2007-2009; cuid39854 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_179)
  - "Evam" Dance by Foofwa d'Imobilite and Azure Carter, 2009; cuid39843 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_165)
  - Dance New Amsterdam - Class and Performance, 2010; cuid39850 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_173)
  - "The Accidental Artist" - SecondLife Performance, Undated; cuid39857 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_229)
  - "Air" Exhibit Photgraphs (Montreal and Toronto), Undated (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - "Blow Dance", Undated; cuid39858 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_230)
  - "Cathedral" - Kira, Azure, Undated; cuid39859 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_231)
  - Dance, Undated (Box 17, Half inch video reel 267_509)
  - Dance 1 and 2 - Heidi Trudinger, Undated (Box 3, U-matic 267_592)
    Other labels on the tape say "Heidi: source for knees piece" and "Heidi Hi8 Dub."
  - "The Death of Sean Smith" Exhibit, Texas, Undated (Box 73, Folder 14, 15)
  - "Flesh" Exhibition - University Gallery, North Carolina, Undated (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - Foofwa d'Imobilite - 3 Solo Excerpts with Commentaries, Undated; cuid39860 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_232)
  - Franklin Furnace Events Calendar, Undated (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Frederic Gafner - Unlabeled Dances, Undated (Box 9, Vhs 267_683, Box 8, Vhs 267_723, Box 68, Folder 19)
  - Geneva Dance Run - Foofwa d'Imobilité, Undated (Box 14, Minidv 267_378)
  - The Ideal Forms: 5 Nude Solo Dances, Undated (Box 17, Half inch video reel 267_533)
  - [Illegible] Ex Habitable with Ellis, Roosevelt Island, Etc., Undated (Box 79, 16mm film reels 267_095)
  - "Kilometrix Dancerun," Foofwa d'Imobilite, Undated; cuid39862 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_234)
  - "Kit I," Meta Ltd., Undated (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - "Projects in Nature: Eleven Environmental Works," Merriewold West, Far Hills, NJ, Undated (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - "Sex Dance", Undated; cuid39863 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_235)
  - Stewart Hannon - Political Tactics and Defense Strategy, Undated; cuid34892 (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_282)
  - Susan Grant Interview, Guitar Solo, Undated; cuid34920 (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_311)
  - Thornton, Greet, Imobilité, Undated (Box 9, Vhs 267_680)
    titles are illegible
  - "Time Stall," Meta Ltd., Undated (Box 73, Folder 18)
- Series VI. Academic Career, 0.5 Linear Feet in 1 manuscript box.; 3 film reels including 1 8mm film and 2 16mm films.; 16 audiocassettes; 1 videocassettes (u-matic)
  Series VI. Academic Career includes lecture notes, instructional materials, syllabi, and audiovisual recordings related to classes taught by Sondheim. It also includes documentation of his engagement with academic conferences and symposiums. Sondheim taught New Media at Florida International University from 2001-2002 and Filmmaking at Brown University from 2006-2007. He frequently gives lectures on multimedia art and cyberspace theory, and has appeared at the Cybermind96 Conference, CyPosium, and South by Southwest.
  - Recorded Correspondence, circa 1955-1965; cuid35086 (Box 23, Quarter inch audio reel 267_107)
    This recorded message on an audiocassette was sent to a family member while Alan was attending undergraduate school in Isreal. He talks about his classes and early career plans.
  - Recorded Correspondence with Acoustic Guitar, circa 1955-1965; cuid35084 (Box 23, Quarter inch audio reel 267_104)
    This recorded message on an audiocassette was sent to a family member while Alan was attending undergraduate school in Israel.
  - Toronto / UCLA, August, 1966; cuid30319 (Box 79, 8mm film reel 267_142)
  - Course Syllabi, 1968-2000 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Halifax Nova Scotia College of Art and Design, 1972; cuid34884 (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_273)
  - The Mezzanine Magazine, Nova Scotia College of Art and Design, May, 1972 (Box 83, Folder 18)
    The Mezzanine was an exhibition space at the Nova Scotia College of Art and Design. This magazine advertises an exhibition by Meta Ltd. on the first page, and lists Alan Sondheim as one of the artists connected with the Mezzanine.
  - "Quinn on Quine" Faculty Systems Group, November 20, 1972; cuid34879 (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_256, 267_262, Box 12, Audiocassette 267_267)
  - Alan Sondheim at USCD, May 23, 1974; cuid34940 (Box 12, Audiocassette 267_210, Box 14, Audiocassette 267_364)
  - Curricula Vitae, 1974-1990 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Instructional Materials, 1975-2000 (Box 70, Folder 7, 8)
  - Art and Ideology Conference - Preliminary Notes, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - "Critique on the Authentic" read at the Ottawa Art and Ideology Conference, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Pre Convention I and II, August 6, 1981; cuid35037 (Box 13, Audiocassette 267_194)
    Duration: 95 minutes; Preservation note: Content drops in audio quality when it switches from music to talk.
  - Black Mountain College Course Listing Brochure, 1989 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - "Images: Between Art and Life" Lecture Series Poster, 1990 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Course Syllabi, 1994-2009; cuid39833 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_189)
  - Instructional Materials, 1994-2009; cuid39834 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_190)
  - Resumes, CVs, and Bios, 1994-2009; cuid39838 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_194)
  - "Mechanical Planet: Genealogies of Virtual Culture" Online Workshop, 1995; cuid39826 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_182)
  - Academic Correspondence, 1995-2007; cuid39828 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_184)
  - Research Proposals and Grant Related Documents, 1995-2009; cuid39837 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_193)
  - Cybermind Conference, 1996; cuid39822 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_172)
  - Cybermind Conference Poster, 1996 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Lectures - Photographs and Notes, 1996-2009; cuid39835 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_191)
  - Conferences and Symposiums - Notes and Documents, 1997-2009; cuid39831 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_187)
  - Webbed Poets Workshop, Albany, 2000; cuid39839 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_195)
  - Conferences and Symposiums - Photographs, 2000-2006; cuid39832 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_188)
  - E-Poetry Photographs, 2001; cuid39823 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_176)
  - "Work on Code" White Paper, 2002-2008; cuid39827 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_183)
  - West Virginia University - Events and Projects, 2004-2009; cuid39840 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_196)
  - Codework Resource Kit, 2005; cuid39829 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_185)
  - E-Poetry Symposium II, 2006; cuid39824 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_177)
  - Brown University MCM 170 Class, c. 2007 (Box 81, 16mm film reels 267_040)
  - Brown University Intro Film, c. 2007 (Box 79, 16mm film reels 267_041)
  - Electronic Media and Film NYSCA Grant Application, 2007 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - "AG Asia Pacific Bounce" Event at West Virginia University, 2008; cuid39825 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_181)
  - Codework Workshop - Schedule of Events, 2008; cuid39830 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_186)
  - Interrupt Conference Poster, 2008 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Interrupt: Language-Driven Digital Art Festival, 2008 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - National Science Foundation (NSF) Conference - Notes and Audio Recordings, 2008; cuid39836 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_192)
  - Alan Discussing Theory As He Walks Through New York City, Plays the Guitar, Undated; cuid35080 (Box 13, Audiocassette 267_153)
  - Alan Talking about Meta's Art / Research Thinktank, Undated; cuid35073 (Box 12, Audiocassette 267_233)
  - Cal Arts, Undated; cuid34882 (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_271, 267_298)
    Duration: 59 minutes; Audiocassette 267_271 could not be digitized due to hydrolysis.
  - Class on Music at Newcastle, Conducted with Stuart Marshall, Undated; cuid34867 (Box 14, Audiocassette 267_362, Audiocassette 267_265)
  - Halifax Convention, Undated; cuid34928 (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_318)
  - Humanities, Arts, Science, and Technology Advanced Collaboratory Conference (HASTAC) - Schedule and Conference Information, Undated (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Institute for the Future Notes, Undated; cuid34914 (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_306)
  - Lecture on Photography - Newcastle, Undated; cuid34933 (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_323)
  - Lecture Posters -- "Post-Conceptual Art" and "Recent Work", Undated (Box 84, Folder 16)
    "Post-Conceptual Art" lecture given at the Liberal Arts Division on March 19th; "Recent Work" lecture sponsored by the Idea Art Workshop and given on March 19th. College and year unknown.
  - Notes - Full Explanation?, Undated; cuid34943 (Box 12, Audiocassette 267_213)
    Duration: 59 minutes; Preservation note: the audio becomes increasingly muffled as the recording goes on.
  - Rhode Island School of Design English Class, Undated; cuid34965 (Box 12, Audiocassette 267_242)
    Duration: 24 minutes.
  - Speech Tape, Undated; cuid34895 (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_286)
- Computer Program Backups, 1988-2007 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_197)